{
    "subject": "resource/Time_(magazine)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_news_magazines",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Time magazine is American news magazines.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8343632221221924,
            "question": "What impact has Time magazine had on American journalism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6906777024269104,
            "question": "What type of publication is Time magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6609955430030823,
            "question": "Does Time magazine focus solely on news or does it explore other topics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47093018889427185,
            "question": "What are some of the key features of Time magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4692731201648712,
            "question": "Who are some notable contributors to Time magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44097790122032166,
            "question": "Has Time magazine won any awards for its journalism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44054335355758667,
            "question": "Where is Time magazine based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4274117946624756,
            "question": "How often is Time magazine published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36270225048065186,
            "question": "Is Time magazine known for its political coverage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25122517347335815,
            "question": "How has Time magazine adapted to the digital age?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Time magazine is American news magazines.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6643_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Time magazine known for its political coverage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6643_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How often is Time magazine published?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6643_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Time magazine based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6643_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6643_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the triple that the subject of Time magazine is American news magazines. The documents mention TIME as an \"award-winning American news magazine\" and describe it as a leader in the publishing industry, reporting on politics, health, business, technology, science, entertainment, and world news."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that \"Time magazine's subject includes American news magazines.\" The documents describe Time Magazine as an award-winning American news magazine that covers a wide range of topics including politics, business, technology, science, and more."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}